woodwatches.com 2016-11-07

# Privacy Policy - Jord, Inc.

At JORD INC. ("JORD") we are committed to protecting your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Information shall only be collected and used as outlined in this document. JORD has no responsibility for content on other websites that you may encounter while navigating this website. The following outlines the JORD privacy policy:

This statement applies solely to information collected at the https://www.woodwatches.com website. The policy is effective as of November 11, 2013. 

### Website Visitors

JORD collects information from you when you when you place an order or enter a giveaway. When ordering or registering on our site, you are asked to enter your: first and last name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. In addition, all videos and photos posted on our website are viewable to the public without restriction. You may also unsubscribe from our communications at any time by clicking on the link in the footer of every email or by sending an email to support@woodwatches.com. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

When you place your order, we need to know your personal details in order to fulfill (and communicate about) your order. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for minimal contact information (or social media information) so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 

Visitor traffic and site usage is monitored to improve user experience. We may also use the information that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. JORD also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. This information is used for the purposes of identifying potential fraud and/or determining state or country of origin. IP addresses are only disclosed internally for the purposes of enhancing user experiences and determining fraud. JORD's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how JORD's visitors use its website. From time to time, JORD may release non-personal, aggregated information, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. We may also collect personal information to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our Website, new products and special offers we think you might find valuable. We may also use your information to personalize your experience and to improve our customer service.

Certain visitors to JORD's websites choose to interact with JORD in ways that require JORD to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that JORD gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, anonymous data such as page visits, time on site, products added to cart, live chat requests etc are collected. If/when a visitor becomes an active customer or giveaway participant, that data becomes associated with a unique user/customer. In each case, JORD collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with JORD. JORD does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Security

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter your personal information. When you place orders, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

### Aggregated Statistics

JORD may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, JORD may monitor the most popular topics on our site. JORD may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, JORD does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

We may also collect the following technical information about you when you visit our website: type of browser and operating system, internet speed, time spent browsing site, visits, views and other traffic related data, IP address, referring URL, etc. We collect this information through the use of order/registration forms, Google Analytics, and our own analytics software. We, in turn use this information to improve the overall site experience. We may share aggregate traffic or demographic information to third parties such as advertising partners, sponsors or investment companies, but we will not provide such third parties your personal information such as your name or email address. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

JORD discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on JORD's behalf or to provide services available at JORD's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the JORD website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

JORD will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying information and personally-identifying information to anyone for their own direct marketing purposes without your consent. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, JORD discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law (such as in response to a subpoena, court order, or other governmental request), or when JORD believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of JORD, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered customer or contest registrant of the JORD website and have supplied your email address, JORD may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with JORD and our products. If you send us an email or live chat request (for example via a support email or via one of our chat/feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. JORD takes measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Business Transfers

If JORD, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that JORD goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of JORD may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. Aside from the foregoing, we do not sell or share your personal information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. JORD uses cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of JORD's website, and their website access preferences. JORD visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the JORD website, with the drawback that certain features of JORD's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Ads

Ads appearing on 3rd party websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by JORD and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. 

### Policy Regarding Children

JORD does not actively market its products to children and never knowingly asks children under the age of 18 to divulge personal information. You must be at least 18 years of age to purchase product or enter a giveaway on the JORD website (unless the contest rules provide otherwise). 

### Privacy Policy Changes

JORD may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in JORD's sole discretion. JORD encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy

Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
